A Finding Aid to the Millard Sheets Papers, 1907-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.sheemill
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, 1956-1981, undated; Series 6; (boxes 9-18; 8.25 linear ft.)
  - Hollywood Turf Club, Inglewood, Calif., 1966-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691-5692)
  - Home Savings and Loan Association, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 12, Reel 5692)
    - Branch Offices (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Ahmanson Center, 1971-1976, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Alhambra, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Anaheim, 1969-1971, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Arcadia, 1975 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Balboa Park (Pacific Beach), 1977 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Barstow, 1975-1977, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Berkeley (Bloom remodel), 1976-1977, undated; (2 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Beverly Hills, 1966-1977, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Buena Park, 1976-1979, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Burbank, 1977 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Century City, 1977 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Compton, 1979 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Cupertino, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Encino, 1973-1977, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Fremont, 1973-1977, undated; (2 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Fresno, 1976 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Garden Grove, 1973-1976, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Grossmont, 1975-1977, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Highland Park, 1973-1974, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Hollywood, Contracts, 1967-1977 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Holywood, Correspondence, 1966-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Hollywood, Job costs and billing statements, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Hollywood, Names for lettering, 1967-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5692)
      - Hollywood, Notes, drawings, photographs, and promotional materials, 1967-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Home office, 1967 (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Huntington Harbor, 1979, undated; (2 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Huntington Park, 1975-1976, undated (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - La Mirada, 1976-1979, undated (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Lakewood, 1975-1979, undated (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Long Beach, Correspondence, 1977-1980, undated (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Long Beach, Miscellaneous background material, 1963, 1977-1980, undated (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Long Beach, Notes and drawings, undated (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Los Angeles (temporary downtown structure), 1974 (Box 12, Reel 5693)
      - Menlo Park, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Montebello (see also Series 6, Branch Offices, Rolling Hills, 1972-1974, undated), (2 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Mountain View, Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Mountain View, Job costs and billing statements, 1974-1978 (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Mountain View, Miscellaneous background material, 1973-1976, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Mountain View, Notes and drawings, 1974-1978, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Newport Beach (Irvine), 1974-1979, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Novato, 1970-1972, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Oakland (18th Street), undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Redlands, 1976-1980, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Redwood City, 1973, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Rialto, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Riverside, 1973 (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Rolling Hills, Correspondence (see also Series 6, Branch Offices, Montebello, 1972-1974), 1972-1974, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Rolling Hills, Job costs and billing statements (see also Series 6, Branch Offices, Montebello, 1972-1974) (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Rolling Hills, Notes and drawings (see also Series 6, Branch Offices, Montebello, 1972-1974), 1973, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693)
      - Santa Ana, 1965-1967, undated (Box 13, Reel 5693-5694)
      - Sacramento, Point West building, Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - Sacramento, Point West building, Job costs and billing statements, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - Sacramento, Point West building, Notes, drawings, and miscellaneous background material, 1972-1976, undated (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - Sacramento, 10th and L Streets building, 1977, undated (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - San Bernardino, 1971-1974, undated; (2 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - San Diego, 1971-1977, undated (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - San Francisco, Correspondence, 1973-1977; (2 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - San Francisco, Job costs and billing statements, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - San Francisco, Notes, drawings and miscellaneous background material, 1962, 1971-1976, undated (Box 13, Reel 5694)
      - San Gabriel, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Reel 5694)
      - San Jose, 1971-1972, undated (Box 14, Reel 5694)
      - Santa Cruz, Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 14, Reel 5694)
      - Santa Cruz, Job costs and billing statements, 1973-1978, undated (Box 14, Reel 5694)
      - Santa Cruz, Notes, drawings, and miscellaneous background material, 1973-1977, undated (Box 14, Reel 5694)
      - Branch Offices, Santa Maria, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Reel 5694)
      - Santa Monica, 1968-1971, undated (Box 14, Reel 5694)
      - Simi Valley, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Reel 5694-5695)
      - Studio City, 1966-1969, 1977, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Tiburon, Clippings (see Series 12, Home Savings and Loan Association, Tiburon branch, Tiburon, Calif., 1973-1976) (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Tiburon, Correspondence, 1972-1980, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Tiburon, Job costs and billing statements, 1972-1980 (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Tiburon, Notes, drawings, and miscellaneous background material, 1966, 1970-1973, undated; (2 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Torrance, 1976-1980, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Tujunga, 1978-1979, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Vacaville, 1976, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Valencia, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Vallejo, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Walnut Creek, 1973-1976, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - West Portal, 1973-1977, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Westminster, 1976-1980, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Westlake Village, 1966, 1976-1980, undated; (2 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5695)
      - Whittier, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Reel 5695)
    - Building Committee minutes of meetings and reports, 1976-1977; (3 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5695)
    - Flow charts, 1977 (Box 14, Reel 5695)
    - Imperial Bank horse sculpture, 1975 (Box 14, Reel 5695)
    - Miscellaneous background material, 1961-1977, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
    - Shields and signs, 1972, undated (Box 14, Reel 5695)
    - Status reports, 1976 (Box 14, Reel 5696)
    - Temporary modular structure, 1975-1976, undated (Box 14, Reel 5696)
  - Hunter, Joseph, residence, Anchor Bay, Calif., 1964 (Box 14, Reel 5696)
  - Hunter, R.O., Jurupa Estates residence, 1969 (Box 14, Reel 5696)
  - International Pipe & Ceramics Corporation (Interpace), Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 14, Reel 5696)
    - Agendas and minutes of meetings, 1964-1971 (Box 14, Reel 5696)
    - Annual reports, 1962-1970 (Box 14, Reel 5696)
    - Coco Palms Mural, Kauai, Hawaii, 1968-1971, undated (Box 14, Reel 5696)
    - Contract and position description, 1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5696)
    - Correspondence (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Adleta Show Case & Fixture Manufacturing Company, 1965 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Betts, John F., 1963-1972 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Bowler, C.N., Jr., 1964-1967 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Choo, Yoon, 1971 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Filsinger, E. Phil, 1958-1971 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Folks, Eugene, F., 1964-1967 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Goodrich, Hobert R., 1961-1967 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Hirsh, Allan M., Jr., (see also Series 2, Hirsh, Mr. & Mrs. Allan M., Jr., 1965-1971), 1963-1967 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - House, Elliot M., 1965-1967, undated (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Kennison, Hugh F., 1963-1973, undated (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Lawton, Richard C., 1963-1965 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Loder, Marc, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Maloof, Sam, 1966 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - McComas, Owen L., 1963-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Miscellaneous, 1961-1973; (2 folders) (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Moffitt, David S., 1963-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Pulling, Richard K., 1971 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Seton, Louis H., 1963-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Stanton, Sheridan G., 1964-1971 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Swanson, Harold V., 1964-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Wagner, Jack L., 1964-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
      - Whitmore, C. F., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5696)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1966-1974, undated (Box 15, Reel 5696)
    - Miscellaneous background material, 1965-1969, undated (Box 15, Reel 5696)
    - Notes and drawings, 1959, 1962-1973, undated (Box 15, Reel 5696-5697)
    - Photographs (see Series 12), 1963-1965, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Johnson, Robert, residence, Escondido, Calif., 1966-1969 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Keenan, Mr. & Mrs. Thomas B., residence and stables, Claremont, Calif., 1968-1969 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Kosa, Emil J., residence, 1968 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Los Angeles County Arboretum, Arcadia, Calif., 1968-1971 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Los Feliz Inn, Los Angeles, Calif., 1975 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Loyola University of Los Angeles, Los Angeles, Calif., 1963-1966, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Lubbock National Bank, Lubbock, Tex. (Box 15, Reel 5697)
    - Charles E. Maedgen, Jr. Memorial Surgical Waiting Room, Methodist Hospital, Lubbock, Tex., 1973-1974 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
    - Main Branch (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Contract and proposal, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1978; (2 folders) (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Custom Business Interiors (Cal Margulies), 1966-1972 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Drawings, photographs, and promotional material, 1965-1967, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Exterior renovations (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Job costs and billing statements, 1966-1974 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Notes, 1965-1972, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
      - Third floor additions, 1971-1972, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
    - Southwest Lubbock National Bank, Lubbock, Tex., 1977-1978, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Malone Ranch, Riverside County, Calif., 1961-1966, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Masi, Mr. & Mrs. Sebastian, residence, Cucamonga, Calif., 1964-1966, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Medallion Restaurant, Los Angeles, Calif., 1973, undated (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Mercantile National Bank, Dallas, Tex., 1958, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Merit Development Company, San Francisco, Calif., 1964 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - Mt. San Antonio College, Walnut, Calif., 1966-1968 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - National Paint and Coatings Association, 1975 (Box 15, Reel 5697)
  - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception, Washington, D.C., 1962-1971, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Contract and job specifications, 1964 (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1971, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - General, 1964-1970 (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Maginnis and Walsh and Kennedy, Boston, Mass., 1963-1974, undated; (2 folders) (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Ravenna Mosaic Company, St. Louis, Mo., 1965-1971 (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Drawings, notes, and research material, 1962-1968, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1964-1969 (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Photographs (see Series 12), 1967-1969, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
  - "Native Diver" memorial, Hollywood Park, Inglewood, Calif., 1968-1970, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
  - Notre Dame mural ("Word of Life"), University of Notre Dame, Notre Dame, Ind., 1962-1968, 1987-1988, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
  - Padelford, Mrs. Louise, residence, Claremont, Calif., 1966-1967, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
  - Perino's Restaurant, Los Angeles, Calif. (see also Series 6, Pierce National Life Insurance Company, 1966-1969, undated), 1967 (Box 16, Reel 5697)
  - Perpetual Savings and Loan Association, Beverly Hills, Calif., 1966 (Box 16, Reel 5697)
  - Person, Roy, residence, 1974, undated (Box 16, Reel 5697)
  - Philibosian, Mrs. Sirpuhe, residence (Box 16, Reel 5697)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Reel 5697-5698)
    - Job Costs, "Desert" house, 1965-1966, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Job Costs, "Persian" house, 1965 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Notes, drawings, and miscellaneous material, 1965-1967, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
  - Pierce National Life Insurance Company, Los Angeles, Calif. (see also Series 6, Perino's Restaurant, Los Angeles, Calif., 1967) (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Bids, 1967-1968, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Job costs, 1966-1969, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Notes, drawings, and miscellaneous material, 1966-1968, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
  - Pomona, City of, Mall and redevelopment project (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Clippings (see Series 12, same heading), 1936-1992, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Contracts and proposals, 1959-1965 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Correspondence, Alvin, Joe, 1960-1963, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Correspondence, General, 1956-1971; (2 folders) (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Correspondence, Sharp, Frederick W., 1959-1971 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1959-1965 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Miscellaneous background material, 1958-1976, undated; (3 folders) (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Notes and drawings, 1960-1966, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Parking lot and landscaping, 1960-1962 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Photographs (see also Series 13) (Box 16, Reel 5698)
  - Pomona First Federal Savings and Loan Association, Pomona, Calif. (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Claremont Architectural Commission, minutes of meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Contracts and proposals, 1968-1979 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Correspondence, Berry Construction Company, Ontario, Calif., 1968-1969 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Correspondence, General, 1965-1979 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Correspondence, Lee, Joseph P., 1967-1969 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Drawings and sketches, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1965-1969, 1976 (Box 16, Reel 5698)
    - Miscellaneous background material, 1968-1969, undated (Box 16, Reel 5698)
  - Porter Ranch entry, Macco Realty Company, Newport Beach, Calif., 1964-1966 (Box 16, Reel 5699)
  - Rainier, F.E. ("Buzz") and Barbara, residence, Carmel, Calif., 1969-1971 (Box 16, Reel 5699)
  - Richard Hardin & Associates, proposal, Austin, Tex., 1971 (Box 16, Reel 5699)
  - Roberts, Dr. & Mrs. Ernest R., residence, 1967 (Box 16, Reel 5699)
  - Ruddick, Mrs. Harold M.., residence, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Reel 5699)
  - St. Joseph's Church, Upland, Calif., 1979-1980, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - St. Paul Civic Center, I. A. O'Shaughnessey Plaza fountain, St. Paul, Minn., 1973 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - San Antonio Plaza fountain, San Antonio, Texas, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - San Jacinto Savings Association, Houston, Texas (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1967; (2 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Notes and miscellaneous background material, 1964-1965, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Photographs (see Series 12, same heading), circa 1966 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - San Jose Mercury News (San Jose Air Terminal mural), 1976-1977 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - Santa Rosa Savings & Loan Association, Santa Rosa, Calif. (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1972; (2 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Field inspection reports, 1968 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Notes, drawings, and miscellaneous background material, 1957, 1967-1969, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - Scottish Rite Masonic Temple, Los Angeles, Calif., 1964-1970 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - Scripps College, Claremont, Calif. (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Architectural contract for Humanities Building, 1967-1968, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - President's Suite, 1967, 1971, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - Shriners Hospital for Crippled Children, San Francisco, Calif., 1969-1971, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - Southern California Edison Company, Los Angeles, Calif., 1971-1973, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
  - Southern California Savings and Loan Association, Beverly Hills, Calif. (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Bruner Pacific (marble), 1968-1969 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Buckeye Realty and Management Corp., 1968-1969, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Carpets, furniture, and lighting, 1969-1970, undated (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Columbia Showcase and Cabinet Company, 1969 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Pinton Freres (tapestries), 1968-1969 (Box 17, Reel 5699)
    - Requests to bid, 1969 (Box 17, Reel 5699-5670)
    - Resolution, 1970 (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Wilshire & Doheny branch office, 1968-1970, undated (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Stone, Ralph, addition to residence, Santa Rosa, Calif., 1970-1971, undated (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Sunset Magazine (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Christmas card painting (see also Series 11, Sunset Magazine, Christmas card text, 1973) (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Dining room mural, Menlo Park, Calif., 1973 (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Travis Savings and Loan Association, San Antonio, Tex. (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1975, undated; (2 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Design sketches, architectural drawings, and photographs, 1966-1968, undated (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Job costs, 1966-1969, undated (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Notes and research material, 1966-1970, undated (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Travis sculpture, 1965 (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Truman's Restaurant and Drive In, Los Angeles, Calif., 1964-1971, undated; (2 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - United Air Lines calendars, 1963-1967 (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Upland Woods housing complex, Upland, Calif., 1977, undated (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Warner Brown Hospital, El Dorado, Ark., circa 1975 (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Washington Cathedral/Mount Saint Alban, Washington, D.C., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Reel 5670)
  - Webb School of California, Claremont, Calif. (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Change orders and credit memos, 1965-1967, undated (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Contracts and proposals, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Reel 5670)
    - Correspondence, Bayne, Peter F., 1965-1968 (Box 18, Reel 5670)
    - Correspondence, General, 1965-1978 (Box 18, Reel 5670)
    - Correspondence, Hooper, Frederick R., 1965-1973 (Box 18, Reel 5670)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1965-1967, undated (Box 18, Reel 5670)
    - Liens and work releases, 1966 (Box 18, Reel 5670)
    - Miscellaneous background material, 1965-1975, undated (Box 18, Reel 5670)
    - Notes and drawings, 1965-1966, undated (Box 18, Reel 5670)
- Teaching and Workshop Files, 1932-1982, undated; Series 7; (box 18; 0.5 linear ft.)
  The material in this series primarily reflects Sheets's teaching activities in an academic setting and his role as an instructor through specialized art workshops. Although Sheets was a professor for many years at Scripps College, few of his academic records from that institution can be found in this collection.
  The series is organized into two subseries:
  7.1: Teaching Positions and Seminars, 1932-1982, undated
  7.2: Workshops, 1952, 1964-1982, undated
  The files are arranged alphabetically by name of institution or subject and then ordered chronologically. In 7.1 the material is further grouped by type of document under the heading for Scripps College. In 7.2 the material is further grouped by date of workshop where there are multiple listings for the institution or program heading.
  - Teaching Positions and Seminars, 1932-1982, undated; 7.1
    The files in 7.1 predominantly reflect short term teaching/lectures given at various Western universities or colleges.
    - Crafton Hills College, Yucaipa, Calif., 1974-1979, undated (Box 18, Reel 5700)
    - Miscellaneous teaching positions, 1948-1952 (Box 18, Reel 5700)
    - Southern Oregon College, Ashland, Ore., 1974-1979, undated (Box 18, Reel 5700)
    - Scripps College, Claremont, Calif. (Box 18, Reel 5700)
      - Correspondence, 1932-1933, 1964-1982 (Box 18, Reel 5700)
      - Lectures and notes, 1946-1950, undated (Box 18, Reel 5700)
      - Miscellaneous related material, 1941, 1963-1986, undated (Box 18, Reel 5700-5701)
      - Scripps College Bulletin, 1938, 1966, 1977-1987 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Vision and Art, KVCR TV series, "A Mural for Spring,", May 21-23, 1968 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - Workshops, 1952, 1964-1982, undated; 7.2
    The files in 7.2 document Sheets's extensive teaching experience as a painting instructor, as evidenced through the numerous workshops he led in the Western United States and Mexico, as well as throughout the world. Researchers will find it useful to also peruse Series 8: Painting trips, 1959-1980, undated for related personal painting trips that often followed Sheets's workshops.
    For additional information about the New Mexico Watercolor Society in Albuquerque, New Mexico, see also Series 10 (Jury files), Oct. 10-11, 1975 "Watercolor Southwest," Western Federation of Watercolor Societies, Museum of Albuquerque, Albuquerque, N. Mex.
    - Alaska Artists' Guild, University of Alaska Drawing/Painting Lab, Anchorage, Alaska, Aug. 16-22, 1982 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Beverly Hills Art League, Roxbury Recreational Center, Beverly Hills, Calif., Mar. 11, 1971 and Sept. 4, 1973 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - City of Fremont, Department of Recreation & Leisure Services, Fremont, Calif., Oct. 24-26, 1980 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Fresno Arts Center, Fresno, Calif., Apr. 4-6, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Hewitt Painting Workshops (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Taxco, Mexico, Aug. 16-28, 1964 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Greek Islands and Istanbul, Turkey, Oct. 7-26, 1965 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - San Miguel Allende, Mexico, July 31-Aug. 12, 1966 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - HAtami, Kyoto, and the Inland Sea, Japan, Oct. 8-29, 1967 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Taxco, Mexico, Aug. 4-16, 1968 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Connemara and Dublin, Ireland, July 9-25, 1969 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Guadalajara, Morelia, and Pátzcuaro, Mexico, Aug. 2-15, 1970 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Greece and Yugoslavia, Sept. 21-Oct. 11, 1971 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Tahiti and New Zealand (see also Series 8, Tahiti, New Zealand, and Fiji, Feb. 24-Apr. 1973), Feb. 24-Mar. 17, 1973 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Gualala and San Francisco, Calif., Oct. 11, 1974 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Yucatan, Mexico and Guatemala, Nov. 3-17, 1974 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - China (canceled), Aug. 29-Sept. 18, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Cabo San Lucas, Mexico, Nov. 8-20, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Moorea and Papeete, Tahiti, May 7-23, 1976 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Gualala, Calif., Oct. 6-15, 1977 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Hawaii, Nov. 1977 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Portugal and Provence, France, Apr. 18-May 2, 1978 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Ajijic, Mexico, Mar. 11-31, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - China, June 17-July 9, 1980 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Invitations, declined, 1952, 1966-1981 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Jade Fon Workshops, Asilomar, Calif., July 7-16, 1976 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Jade Fon Workshops, Asilomar, Calif., June 28-July 8, 1977 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Letters of appreciation from workshop participants, 1971-1978, undated (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Mid-Southern Watercolorists, Little Rock, Ark., May 21-26, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - New Mexico Watercolor Society, Albuquerque, N. Mex. (Box 18, Reel 5701)